Viewers all over the world, that pain - cease, in the name of Jesus!
You affliction, leave my people!
Wherever it is located in your body, whatever name you call it -
I command you out, in the name of Jesus!
Right now, dismiss that thought - that thought of satan, dismiss it in your heart!
Begin to dismiss it right now.
Jesus says you are healed and if Jesus says you are healed, you are healed!
Dismiss that thought!
Dismiss that thought in your heart - dismiss it!
I'm healed!
In the name of Jesus Christ!
Viewers, breakthrough, in the name of Jesus!
Stretch your hand and touch your business!
Touch your career!
Touch your marriage!
Your families, finances, business partner - breakthrough, in the name of Jesus!
Breakthrough, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch The Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Right now, begin to confess breakthrough.
Confess breakthrough!
In the mighty name of Jesus!
TT: Mel Flowers 18/11/2018
RV: Pavel Tatyana Zheleznyakov 23/11/2018